&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：在这一点上，你肯定会问自己，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: You certainly must be asking yourself at this point,
但是，箭头函数呢？
but, what about arrow functions?
我们的好朋友箭头功能。
Our good friend the arrow function.
让我们回到箭头函数并在以下上下文中检查它们
Let's come back to arrow functions and examine them within the context of what
我们刚才已经讨论过了，这就是this关键字。
we've just discussed, which is the this keyword.
在这里，您会注意到我在工作坊对象上有一个ask方法。
Here you'll notice that I have an ask method on my workshop object.
在它内部，我对setTimeout和
And inside of it, I'm making a callback pass to setTimeout and
这是一个箭头函数。
it's an arrow function.
并且这个关键字，当箭头函数被调用时，
And that this keyword, when the arrow function is invoked,
正确地指向车间对象。
is correctly is pointing at the workshop object.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这就是我们所说的词法这个行为。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: This is what we refer to as lexical this behavior.
所以让我清楚地告诉你这意味着什么，
So let me clearly state for you what lexical this means,
关于这个话题有很多混淆。
there's a lot of confusion around this topic.
许多人的脑海中都有这样一种心理模型
Many people have in their minds a mental model that
箭头函数本质上是硬绑定函数
a arrow function is essentially a hardbound function
对父母来说这，那是不准确的。
to the parents this, that is not accurate.
思考箭头函数是什么的正确方式，
The proper way to think about what an arrow function is,
箭头函数根本没有定义this关键字。
an arrow function does not define a this keyword at all.
箭头函数中没有this关键字这样的东西。
There is no such thing as a this keyword in an arrow function.
这意味着如果将this关键字放在箭头函数中，
Which means if you put a this keyword inside of an arrow function,
它的行为就像任何其他变量一样。
it's gonna behave exactly like any other variable.
这意味着它将在词汇上解析为某种封闭
Which means it's going to lexically resolve to some enclosing
定义此关键字的范围。
scope that does define of this key word.
所以当这个特殊的情况，箭头函数行5，当我们说
So when this particular case, the arrow function line 5, when we say
这个点在箭头函数中没有这个，无论它是如何调用的，所以
this dot there is no this in that arrow function no matter how it gets invoked, so
我们在词汇上升了一个层次的范围，也就是，哪个功能？
we lexically go up one level of scope which is, which function?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：[听不到]。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [INAUDIBLE].
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：Ask函数。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The ask function.
车间不是一个功能，车间是一个对象。
Workshop is not a function, workshop is an object.
它从回调函数，箭头函数，
It goes out from the call back function, the arrow function,
范围到封闭范围，是什么？
that scope to the enclosing scope, which is?
问，问这个关键词的定义是什么？
Ask, and what is asks definition of the this key word?
哪一行代码控制着this关键字将在ask中指出的内容。
What line of code controls what the this keyword will point out inside of ask.
第10行，因为ask函数这个关键字是由调用站点设置的。
Line 10, because the ask functions this keyword gets set by the call site.
然后当该回调稍后被调用时，它基本上是关闭的。
And then when that call back gets later invoked, it’s essentially closed over.
具有指向工作坊对象的this关键字的父作用域。
That parent scope that had a this keyword pointing at the workshop object.
这就是我们所说的词汇this的意思。
That's what we mean by lexical this.
它不是硬绑定函数。
It's not a hard bound function.
它是一个完全没有this的函数。
It's a function that doesn't have a this at all.
所以它在词汇上旋转，这意味着如果它必须上升，五个层次，因为
And so it revolves lexically, that means if it had to go up, five levels because
你有五个嵌套的箭头函数，它一直在不断上升
you had five nested arrow functions, it just keeps going and going and going up
建筑电梯直到找到定义this关键字的函数。
the building elevator until it finds a function that defines a this keyword.
无论this关键字针对该函数指向什么，这就是它所使用的。
And whatever the this keyword points at for that function, that's what it uses.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这不是描述它的正确解释
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That is just not the correct explanation to describe it and
最近很多人在推特上和我争论说，
many people have been arguing with me recently on Twitter saying,
，但这无关紧要。
,but it doesn't matter.
是的，这是说明书，说明书上说，
Yes it does and here is the spec, the spec says,
箭头函数没有为定义局部绑定
an arrow function does not define local bindings for
参数超过this或new.target。
arguments super this or new.target.
人们有时喜欢射杀信使。
People sometimes like to shoot the messenger.
规格不是我写的。
I didn't write the spec.
我只是告诉你说明书上说了什么，好吗？
I'm just telling you what the spec says, okay?
规范说没有this关键字。
The spec says there is no this keyword.
所以我认为对你来说最好的结果是当你像电脑一样思考
So I think the best outcome for you is when you think like the computer instead
试图发明你自己的解释，可能会也可能不会偏离
of trying to invent your own explanations, that may or may not deviate and
创造，并使错误的想法和错误永久化。
create, and perpetuate wrong thinking and bugs.
我在课程的前面已经说过了。
I've said this earlier in the course.
当您错误地思考一段代码如何工作时，
When you think incorrectly about how a piece of code works,
即使它在那一刻偶然起作用，你也是不正确的
even if it accidentally works at that moment, you're incorrect
思考会在系统上导致更多的bug。
thinking will systemically lead to more bugs down the line.
只有一个办法可以解决这个问题。
And there's only one fix for that.
它是思考，就像JavaScript认为的那样。
It's to think, like JavaScript thinks.
这就是为什么我在这门课上一遍又一遍地引用。
That's why I keep referencing in this course over and over and over again.
说明书上说什么？
What does the spec say?
规格说明的内容很重要
And it matters what the spec says so
我们不会让我们的大脑走上错误的轨道去思考一些事情。
that we don't get our brains off on the wrong track and think about something.
你可能认为箭头函数不是硬绑定就不重要了。
You might not think it would ever matter that an arrow function's not hard bound.
好吧，这里有一个非常疯狂的角落案例，它可能很重要。
Well here's a really crazy corner case where it could matter.
还记得这个关键字的行为，
Remember how that this keyword behavior,
new关键字比硬绑定函数更具先例。
the new keyword is more precedent than a hardbound function.
不知为什么，由于某种疯狂的原因，如果你对硬绑定函数调用new，它
That somehow for some crazy reason, if you call new on a hardbound function it
覆盖硬绑定并使其成为新对象。
overrides the hardbound and it makes it the new object.
猜猜当您对箭头函数调用new时会发生什么。
Guess what happens when you call new on an arrow function.
如果箭头函数是硬绑定的，您应该能够在箭头上调用new
If an arrow function's hard bound, you ought to be able to call new on an arrow
函数并重写其this关键字。
function and override its this key word.
当你对箭头函数调用new时会发生什么，以前有人试过吗？
What happens when you call new on an arrow function, anybody ever try that before?
你实际上得到了一个例外。
You actually get an exception.
不允许对箭头函数调用new。
You're not allowed to call new on an arrow function.
所以它不是硬绑定函数。
So it's not a hard bound function.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这是一个没有在此关键字上定义的函数。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It is a function that doesn't define on this keyword.